<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Speaker Cleaner</string>
    <string name="app_description">Remove trapped water and dust from your phone\'s speaker with sound frequencies.</string>
    <string name="volume_warning_title">Volume Warning</string>
    <string name="volume_warning_desc">Please turn your volume to MAXIMUM and place your phone screen down for the best results.</string>
    <string name="btn_auto_clean">Auto Clean (80s)</string>
    <string name="btn_manual_clean">Manual Clean</string>
    <string name="btn_headphone_clean">Headphone Clean (45s)</string>
    <string name="btn_sound_fix">Sound Fix (1000Hz)</string>
    <string name="btn_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="text_remaining">Time Remaining: %1$ds</string>
    <string name="text_frequency">%1$d Hz</string>
    <string name="state_idle">Ready to Clean</string>
    <string name="state_cleaning">Cleaning Active</string>
    <string name="state_complete">Cleaning Completed!</string>
    <string name="state_error">Error: %1$s</string>
    <string name="success_alert_desc">Your speaker has been cleaned successfully. If it still sounds muffled, run Sound Fix or try again.</string>
    <string name="btn_ok">Got it</string>
    <string name="toast_select_language_continue">Please select a language to continue</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="splash_ads_warning">Ads may load shortly, please wait…</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_1_title">Clean Water</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_2_title">Physical Vibration</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_3_title">Air Blow</string>
    <string name="intro_next">Next</string>
    <string name="intro_slide_4_title">Finished!</string>
    <string name="lore_ipsum_tip"></string>

    <!-- Tip 1 -->
    <string name="tip1_title">Turn the Volume to Maximum</string>
    <string name="tip1_desc">Set your phone’s volume to the highest level before starting the cleaning process. The cleaning sound creates strong audio vibrations that help push trapped water droplets, dust, and debris out of the speaker chamber. Higher volume levels generate stronger vibrations, making the cleaning process more effective.\n\nMake sure any Bluetooth devices, headphones, or external speakers are disconnected so the sound plays directly through your phone’s built-in speaker. During cleaning, you may notice water droplets emerging from the speaker opening or slight changes in sound quality. This is normal and indicates that the cleaning sound is working as intended.\n\nIf your speaker has been exposed to a significant amount of water, running multiple cleaning cycles may help remove remaining moisture and restore clearer audio performance.</string>
    <string name="tip1_preview">Set your phone’s volume to the highest level before starting the cleaning process...</string>

    <!-- Tip 2 -->
    <string name="tip2_title">Keep the Speaker Facing Downward</string>
    <string name="tip2_desc">For the best results, always position your phone so the speaker opening faces downward during the cleaning process. Gravity works together with the sound vibrations to help water droplets move out of the speaker chamber more easily.\n\nPlace the device on a stable surface and avoid changing its position while cleaning is active. Keeping the speaker pointed downward helps prevent moisture from settling deeper inside the speaker cavity and improves the effectiveness of each cleaning cycle.\n\nIf your phone has recently been exposed to rain, splashes, or accidental water contact, combining maximum volume with the correct orientation can significantly improve moisture removal and audio recovery.</string>
    <string name="tip2_preview">For the best results, always position your phone so the speaker opening faces downward...</string>

    <!-- Tip 3 -->
    <string name="tip3_title">Clean the Microphone Carefully</string>
    <string name="tip3_desc">The microphone plays a critical role in phone calls, voice recordings, video chats, and voice assistant functions. Over time, dust, lint, and small particles can collect around the microphone opening, reducing voice clarity and affecting overall audio performance.\n\nRegular cleaning helps maintain microphone sensitivity and ensures your voice remains clear during conversations and recordings. If people frequently report that your voice sounds muffled or distant, accumulated debris may be blocking the microphone opening.\n\nAlways clean gently and avoid using excessive force. Sharp tools or aggressive cleaning methods can damage the microphone mesh and internal components. Taking a careful approach helps preserve long-term microphone performance and audio quality.</string>
    <string name="tip3_preview">The microphone plays a critical role in phone calls, voice recordings, video chats...</string>

    <!-- Tip 4 -->
    <string name="tip4_title">Use a Toothpick to Remove Dust or Dirt Carefully</string>
    <string name="tip4_desc">A wooden toothpick can be used to remove visible dust and debris from around the microphone opening. Work slowly and only use the tip near the surface area. The objective is to loosen dirt around the protective mesh without reaching internal components.\n\nUse light, controlled movements and inspect the area under good lighting. Never insert the toothpick deeply into the microphone hole or apply pressure directly inward, as this can damage sensitive parts inside the device.\n\nRemoving small amounts of debris gradually is safer and often more effective than attempting to clean everything at once. With proper care, routine microphone maintenance can improve call quality, enhance voice recordings, and help keep your phone’s audio system performing at its best.</string>
    <string name="tip4_preview">A wooden toothpick can be used to remove visible dust and debris from around the microphone...</string>
</resources>